Guide to the Doris Duke Papers, 1798-2003 and undated (bulk 1930-1999)
Duke University. University Archives
- Financial Records, 1905-1966 and undated
  - General Financial Records, 1905-1996
    - Invoices and purchase information relating to Doris Duke's silver (also silver purchased by her parents). Includes guide to markings, 1905–1939, 1981–1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Analysis of account with Nanaline H. Duke. Includes appraisals of the 78th St. Mansion and Rough Point (1925–1926), 1925–1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Reports on contributions and related letters to Doris Duke thanking her for her generous donations, 1930–1958, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Statements of income from Guaranty Trust Co., statements of transactions, and related correspondence concerning the distribution and final termination of the Walker P. Inman - Doris Duke Trust, 1933–1955 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Vouchers for deposits on property purchases at Lake Mashepacong, N.J., property in Hillsborough, N.J., and purchases made by Walker Inman at Duke Farms for Doris Duke (Husinec and Stryker properties), 1934–1938, 1964, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning purchases made by Doris Duke Cromwell from Japan, China, and the Orient, 1935–1937 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Vouchers for automobile purchases made by Doris Duke, 1935–1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Invoices and related materials for antiques, furnishings, etc. for Doris Duke's various homes, 1935–1982 (1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Invoices and related materials for antiques, furnishings, etc. for Doris Duke's various homes, 1935–1982 (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and memoranda relating to Doris Duke Cromwell's investments and tobacco products reorganization, 1936–1937 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Audit Reports for Mrs. Doris Duke Cromwell while at Shangri La. Prepared by Cameron & Johnstone, Honolulu, 1936–1942 (1 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Audit Reports for Mrs. Doris Duke Cromwell while at Shangri La. Prepared by Cameron & Johnstone, Honolulu, 1936–1942 (2 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Audit Reports for Mrs. Doris Duke Cromwell while at Shangri La. Prepared by Cameron & Johnstone, Honolulu, 1936–1942 (3 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Invoices, vouchers, and receipts relating to the shipment of purchases by Thomas Cook & Son and Hudson Forwarding and Shipping, 1937–1939 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Vouchers for purchase of property at 66–72 West 12th St., N.Y.C. Includes voucher for the matter of the property of Mildred Brett and Ruby Roney, Wilson, N.C., 1937, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Invoices, vouchers, and related materials concerning Doris Duke's purchases for various homes (some photocopies), 1937–1953 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Purchases made for Doris Duke for different houses. Also includes list of items possibly donated from Rough Point, 1937, 1955–1956 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning the purchase of doors for Doris Duke (FL, HI), 1937, 1953–1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence relating to Doris Duke Cromwell's financial assistance to Miss P. Roney and Mrs. L. Brett, her extended family on her father's mother's side. Doris Duke sent money to the women to save their home in Wilson, N.C. House was later sold and loan paid back, 1937–1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for purchase and repairs made to ceramics and porcelain pieces, 1937, 1940, 1963, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Invoices are vouchers relating to conservation and restoration work performed on paintings, 1937, 1968–1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning the purchase and repair of panels and screens (DF, SL, and 1 E. 78th St.), 1937–1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning Doris Duke's rug purchases for various homes, 1937–1983, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence relating to foreign purchases made by Doris Duke, 1938–1953 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Journal entries of Doris Duke's including repairs to Brett-Roney house, residences, antiques purchased by Erno Laszlo for DD, and the Thai House Foundation, 1938–1939, 1948–1961 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning the purchase of mirrors for Doris Duke (NY Apt., LADD Interiors, DF), 1938–1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Invoices and vouchers for sundry purchases made by Doris Duke while in London and Paris (1958). Includes a ledger sheet for payments owed to Leon Amar. Also includes miscellaneous invoices for purchases made by Johnny Gomez, 1938, 1954–1955, 1973–1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning Doris Duke's clothing and antique purchases overseas and other administrative matters, 1938–1939, 1982–1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Analysis of personal expenses of Doris Duke Cromwell, 1939–1940 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Invoices and receipts for glassware purchased at W.G.T. Burne, 1939–1940 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Invoices and receipts for purchases from M. Harris & Sons, 1939–1941 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Invoices, bill of lading, and related materials concerning Doris Duke's purchases of antiques and their shipment to the U.S., 1940 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Invoices and related correspondence concerning furniture purchases made by Doris Duke and her father and mother, without 1 specific location. Houses include 3121 Arlington Dr., Reno, Nevada, 1009 Fifth Ave, and Duke Farms, 1940–1943, 1958, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Analysis of receipts and disbursements for Doris Duke Cromwell, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Invoices from McMillen, Inc. for interior design services for several of Miss Duke's homes, 1941–1954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Invoices of purchases through Sotheby Parke-Bernet for objects in multiple homes, 1941–1955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for purchase of cabinets, cupboards, and dressers for Shangri La, New York Apartment, and New York Mansion, 1942, 1944, 1956, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Invoice for a drawing by Salvador Dali, "Double Head," 1943 Jan 11 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Financial Reports of sales of stock belonging to Doris Duke (Group I), 1945, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports of sales of stock belonging to Doris Duke (Group II and IIA), 1945, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Financial Reports of sales of stock belonging to Doris Duke (Group V and VI), 1945–1951 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Invoice from Lucien Lelong, Paris, for purchase of couture blouses and robes purchased by Doris Duke Cromwell, 1946 May 2 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Financial Reports of sales of stock belonging to Doris Duke (Group III), 1946, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Letter of identification from the Guaranty Trust Company of New York. Includes a statement of account from the Guaranty Trust Company of New York, Paris office, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Vault and security transactions of safe deposit boxes belonging to Doris Duke, 1947–1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Financial ledger pages documenting furniture, fixtures, and decoration costs for the N.Y. Office (home of the Doris Duke Foundation), 1948–1964 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, bills of sale, and other materials relating to Doris Duke's ownership of automobiles, 1949–1971 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Financial Reports of daily sales (Groups I–IV) of stocks and related correspondence, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Financial Reports of sales of stock belonging to Doris Duke (Group IV), 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Invoices, receipts, and related correspondence concerning Doris Duke's foreign purchase and shipments to the U.S., 1950–1963 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York checkbooks with receipt stubs for checks drawn on Doris Duke's account, 1950–1967 (1 of 4) (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York checkbooks with receipt stubs for checks drawn on Doris Duke's account, 1950–1967 (2 of 4) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York checkbooks with receipt stubs for checks drawn on Doris Duke's account, 1950–1967 (3 of 4) (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York checkbooks with receipt stubs for checks drawn on Doris Duke's account, 1950–1967 (4 of 4) (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Personal expenses - Yearly accounts, 1952–1958 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Invoices, miscellaneous, furniture and other materials purchased at Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1952, 1955, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for purchase and shipment of chairs to Dr. Erno Laszlo and The Laszlo Institute, 1954, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Invoices and receipts for purchases sold to Russell McKinnon, probably an agent for Doris Duke, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Checkbook for Doris Duke's account with the Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1955–1956 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Agreements relating to a Bond of $187,500 from Doris Duke to Erno Laszlo and his wife for the purchase of 14 E. 78th St. for The Erno Laszlo Institute, Inc. (1957). Institute will house the Roman Catholic Orphan Asylum in the City of N.Y., 1955–1958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Invoices of purchases through Sotheby Parke-Bernet for objects in multiple homes, 1956–1962 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports of stock sales and purchases of Doris Duke's, 1957–1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Invoice, Valentino Couture, Blue Gazard dress, 1968 Oct 19 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, notices, and copy of Agreement (1958) relating to Doris Duke's creation of a trust for Marie Louise Bousquet, Paris, France, 1958–1961 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Reports on contributions and related letters to Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York for the donation of securities by Doris Duke, 1959–1962 (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Reports on contributions and related letters to Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York for the donation of securities by Doris Duke, 1959–1962 (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Journal, analysis of stock owned by Doris Duke. Also includes DD travel info and poem (DD's handwriting), circa 1960 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Disbursement lists and related documents concerning Marjorie Mohun, Special Acct. held at the Somerville Trust Company, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Receipt from Thierry, Paris, France, insurance for shipment of antiques, 1962 Feb 10 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Invoices of purchases through Sotheby Parke-Bernet for objects in multiple homes, 1962–1965 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning Doris Duke's purchases of antique at auction and elsewhere, 1961–1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Reports on contributions and related letters to Morgan Guaranty Trust Company to donors that received stock or securities from Doris Duke, 1963–1966 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Invoices, receipts, and related correspondence concerning Doris Duke's purchases and shipped to the U.S., 1964–1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda relating to personal checks drawn by Doris Duke, 1964–1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Invoices, receipts, and related correspondence concerning purchases made for Doris Duke and shipped to the U.S. from overseas. Includes badminton mirror and other antiques. Mirror purchased by E. Tirella in 1965 from Mallet & Son, London, 1964–1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Letter to Mr. Cooley from A. Anderson, re: improvement of procedures and accounting records for Miss Duke's accounts 1966 Nov 15 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Stock purchases and recommendations. Includes legend, 1966 (1 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Stock purchases and recommendations. Includes legend, 1966 (2 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Stock purchases and recommendations. Includes legend, 1966 (3 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Legend for monthly investment meetings, operations, stocks, etc. (Copy), 1966 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Invoices of purchases through Sotheby Parke-Bernet for objects in multiple homes, 1966–1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Invoices, vouchers, and related materials concerning mostly personal purchases made by Doris Duke, 1966–1987 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Invoices, vouchers, and related materials concerning mostly personal purchases made by Doris Duke, 1966–1987 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Bank correspondence relating to Doris Duke's account with Morgan Guaranty. Includes receipts noting the transfer of securities from vault to MG custody, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Bank correspondence and newspaper article relating Doris Duke's bank account with La Banque Continentale, 1967–1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Reports on contributions and related letters to Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. on behalf of donors that received stock or securities from Doris Duke, 1967–1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning the cleaning and repair of rugs at all homes, 1967–1985 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Estimate for work to be performed on screens by Eikado East, art restoration specialists, 1968 May 22 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Doris Duke's donations and net worth statement, 1968 Oct (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Summary list of monthly bills for all of Doris Duke's properties, 1968 Dec 10 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Accountants' Report (6) and letter on internal control and accounting procedures prepared by Peat, Marwick, Mitchell, & Co., 1968 (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Letter on internal control and accounting procedures prepared by Peat, Marwick, Mitchell, & Co., 1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Vouchers, special situation stocks, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Receipts and forms relating to Doris Duke's bank account with First National City Bank, Paris branch, 1968–1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Financial statements and related materials concerning Doris Duke's account with Goldman, Sachs & Co., 1968–1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Statements of cash transactions and receipts relating to Doris Duke's purchases and sales of stock and equity, 1968–1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Bonds bought for Doris Duke by the Morgan Guaranty Trust Company. Includes a summary of an African American student group protest on the campus of Duke University, 1969 Feb (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Accountants' Report which includes financial statements and schedules for Doris Duke's estate as of June 30, 1968, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Financial statements of non-taxable bond interest belonging to Doris Duke. Original file read, "Duplicates of statements given to Georgiana Daly of Morgan Guaranty Trust Co.", 1969 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Trial balance, balance sheets of assets, liabilities, and capital of Doris Duke, 1969–1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Bank correspondence and other materials relating to Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1969–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Bank correspondence and other materials relating to Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1969–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Statements of account from First National City Bank in Paris relating to Doris Duke's account, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Bank statements from La Banque Continentale for bank account belonging to Doris Duke, 1970–1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Invoices from Parke-Bernet in the name of Malcolm Vallance for Doris Duke, 1970–1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Inventories of stock portfolios and related correspondence prepared by T. Rowe Price & Associates, Inc. for Doris Duke, 1970–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Inventories of stock portfolios and related correspondence prepared by T. Rowe Price & Associates, Inc. for Doris Duke, 1970–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Bank correspondence, notes, and other materials relating to Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1970–1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Bank correspondence and related materials concerning Doris Duke's bank account with Union Bank of Switzerland, Zurich, 1971–1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Office and deductible expenses and changes in securities, 1971–1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning the repair and maintenance of Doris Duke's fur collection. Also includes invoices for repairs of silver, 1972–1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence to Doris Duke from T. Rowe Price regarding buying and selling recommendations, 1972–1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Invoices, correspondence, and related materials concerning Doris Duke's trip to Thailand (1973). Purchases were made for SEAAC, Mr. Amar, and herself. Other materials relate to an insurance claim by LADD Interiors for cases of antiques damaged while onboard the "Hong Kong Grace", 1973–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Invoices, correspondence, and related materials concerning Doris Duke's trip to Thailand (1973). Purchases were made for SEAAC, Mr. Amar, and herself. Other materials relate to an insurance claim by LADD Interiors for cases of antiques damaged while onboard the "Hong Kong Grace", 1973–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Trial balance, balance sheets of assets, liabilities, and capital of Doris Duke, 1974–1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Invoice and related materials concerning a painting, "Girl Playing a Stringed Instrument," purchased by Leon Amar for Doris Duke at Sotheby Parke-Bernet, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Financial spreadsheets detailing taxes paid for all current properties, 1975–1982 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Receipts from Morgan Guaranty reflecting transactions of Doris Duke's security deposit accounts, 1976–1981 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and related materials relating to the cleaning and repair of rugs at Duke Farms, Shangri La, and Rough Point, 1976-1982 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Statements of accounts and other materials relating to Doris Duke's American Express card, 1976–1986 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Samuel Greenspoon, attorney, 1977–1983 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Bank correspondence and related receipts concerning Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and related materials concerning Doris Duke's donations to the Institute of Spiritual Science. Dr. Florence Zellhofer was contact at the Institute, 1978–1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Bank correspondence and related receipts concerning Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1977–1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Bank correspondence and related receipts concerning Doris Duke's account with Affida Trust Company in Zurich, Switzerland, 1978–1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Bank correspondence and related receipts concerning Doris Duke's account with Morgan Guaranty Trust Company in Zurich, Switzerland, 1978–1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Tax bills for properties at Montague Twp., Sussex County, N.J., Reading Township, N.J., Middletown and Portsmouth, R.I., 1978–1985 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Bank correspondence and related receipts concerning Doris Duke's account with Union Bank of Switzerland, 1979–1983 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Invoices of purchases through Sotheby Parke-Bernet multiple homes, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Franco Rossellini's phone bills that were paid by Doris Duke, 1983–1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Checkbook, Citibank, 1985–1986 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - List of Doris Duke's accounts and stocks held, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by United Airlines, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Municipal Bond portfolio for Doris Duke. Includes Plan of Organization and Purchase Agreement for her 475 Park Avenue Apartment, 1986–1987 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Stock and Bond portfolio completed by Irwin E. Bloom, 1987 Apr (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for purchases made at Bergdorf Goodman, 1988 Oct 25 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Statements of account, estimates, and related materials concerning repairs and conservation made to Doris Duke's rugs by Costikyan, Ltd., 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and related memoranda concerning the purchase of wine presents and cartridges for Wine Cellars at Duke Farms and Shangri La, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Invoices and related materials pertaining to seamstresses and tailoring services provided to Doris Duke, 1991–1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Financial statements, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Financial statements for Doris Duke, Doris Duke Foundation, Doris Duke Charitable Foundation, Newport Restoration Foundation, SEAAC, Duke Gardens Foundation, Duke Farms, and Duke Farms, Inc., prepared by Irwin Bloom for FY 1991, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Invoices for private nurse, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Statements of Doris Duke's financial transactions. Includes charts and graphs for Doris Duke's taxes paid and assets (1986–1991), 1992 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Promotional material as well as a Quarterly Report to shareholders from Bank of America, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Statement of property and bank assets with Chase Manhattan Bank, 1988 Nov 4 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Doris Duke Financial Records, 1987 (Oversize-box 40)
    - Doris Duke Financial Records, 1988 (Oversize-box 41)
    - Doris Duke Financial Records, 1989 (Oversize-box 42)
    - Doris Duke Financial Records, 1990 (Oversize-box 43)
    - Doris Duke Stocks and Bonds Summaries, 1987-1988 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 44)
    - Doris Duke Stocks and Bonds Summaries, 1987-1988 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 45)
    - Doris Duke's Checks from the Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, 1933-1946 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box 46)
    - Doris Duke's Checks from the Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, 1933-1946 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box 47)
    - J.B. Duke Trustee for Doris Duke, regarding Income Tax Returns, 1917 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - J.B. Duke Trustee for Doris Duke, regarding Income Tax Returns, 1918 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - J.B. Duke Trustee for Doris Duke, regarding Income Tax Returns, 1919 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Income Tax - Nanaline H Duke, Guardian of Doris Duke, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1933 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Doris Duke record of purchases and other financial records, 1933-1952 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Gift Tax - Doris Duke, 1933-1964 (1 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Gift Tax - Doris Duke, 1933-1964 (2 of 2) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Honolulu Income Tax Returns - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1941-1944 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke Cromwell, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke (formerly Doris Duke Cromwell), 1946 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1947 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Income Tax - Doris Duke, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 1)